Goodson, William Wilson, Jr., collector. Science fiction fanzines and related papers collected by William Wilson Goodson Jr., 1970-2008 (SF-3136): PRELIMINARY BOX LIST.
William Wilson Goodson Jr. collection of science fiction fanzines and related papers,
1970-2008.
Houghton Library, Harvard College Library, Harvard University
SF-3136
Goodson, William Wilson, Jr., collector.
4.5 linear feet (4 boxes)
Preliminary box list only for science fiction fanzines and related papers collected by William Wilson Goodson Jr.
2014M-118. Gift of William Wilson Goodson Jr.; received: 2015 February 5, September 1.
There are no restrictions on physical access to this material. Collection is open for research.
William Wilson Goodson is an audiovisual specialist in higher education and a researcher, as well as a collector of science fiction.
Arranged in two series: I. Science fiction fanzines, arranged alphabetically by title (titles beginning with "The" are found under the letter "T"); and II. Correspondence and related papers.
Comprised of fanzines (1970-2008); also with correspondence (1974-1987); other fanzines; and convention material.
Additional science fiction material held by the Houghton Library can be found by searching HOLLIS Classic for “SF” as “Other call number”. This will provide a list of all the material specifically in the Science Fiction Collection, but not all material by some science fiction authors in author collections. For this reason, it is often preferable to search by author or title. A finding aid is available for a separate collection of fanzines and prozines, SF 3133.
- I. Science fiction fanzines
  - A
    - Aboriginal Science Fiction: number; 1987 Nov-Dec. (box 4)
      Editor: Charles C Ryan.
    - Aboriginal Science Fiction: number; 1988 March/April. (box 1)
    - Abyss: number 5; 1984 November. (box 1)
      Editor: David Nalle.
    - Adrenalin: number 1; undated. (box 1)
      Editor: John Carl.
    - Adrenalin: number 2; undated. (box 1)
    - Amazing Stories: volume 66, number 1; 1991 May. (box 4)
      Editor: Kim Mohan.
    - Amazing Stories: volume 66, number 2; 1991 June. (box 4)
    - Amazing Stories: volume 66, number 3; 1991 July. (box 4)
    - Amazing Stories: volume 66, number 4; 1991 August. (box 4)
    - Amazing Stories: volume 66, number 5; 1991 September. (box 4)
    - Amazing Stories: volume 71, number 5; 1999 June. (box 4)
    - American Fantasy: volume 2, number 4; 1987 Summer. (box 1)
      Editor: Robert Garcia.
    - Amra: volume 2, number 64; 1975 October. (box 1)
      Editor: L. Sprague de Camp.
    - Amra: volume 2, number 65; 1976. (box 1)
    - Amra: volume 2, number 66; 1976. (box 1)
    - Amra: volume 2, number 67; 1977. (box 1)
    - Amra: volume 2, number 68; 1978 July. (box 1)
    - Amra: volume 2, number 69; 1981 January. (box 1)
    - Amra: volume 2, number 70; 1981 September. (box 1)
    - Amra: volume 2, number 71; 1982 July. (box 1)
    - Antelope Freeway: number; 1981 July 29. (box 1)
      Editor: Chris Martin.
    - APA-H: number 72; 1979 January. (box 1)
    - Apex!: number; 1987 August. (box 1)
      Editor: Ramona Richards.
    - Apex!: number 1; 1987. (box 1)
    - Argonaut: number 10; 1984 Summer. (box 1)
      Editor: Michael Ambrose.
    - Awry: number 6; 1973 December. (box 1)
      Editor: Dave Locke.
  - B - C
    - BackGround Noise: volume 2, number 19; 1980 April 1. (box 1)
      Editor: Jon Slobins.
    - BackGround Noise: volume 2, number 20; 1980 April 27. (box 1)
    - BackGround Noise: volume 2, number 22; 1980 June 21. (box 1)
    - Beyond: number 1; 1985. (box 1)
      Editor: Roberta Ragou.
    - Beyond: number 3; 1986 January. (box 1)
    - Beyond: number 5; 1986 September. (box 1)
    - Beyond: number 8; 1987. (box 1)
    - Beyound the Third Planet: number; 1984. (box 1)
      Editor: Lynne Holden.
    - boing boing: number 14; undated. (box 1)
      Editor: Carja Sincjair.
    - Burger!: number 1; 1971 October. (box 1)
      Editor: Ed Smith.
    - Cao Times: volume 6, number 2; 1985 January 21. (box 1)
      Editor: Al H. Morrison.
    - Carolina Inter National: number 4; 1976 September. (box 1)
    - Chat SFiC News: number 1; 1981 September. (box 1)
      Editor: Andre Barker-Bridget.
    - Comic Reader: volume 1, number 101; 1973 november. (box 1)
      Editor: Jerome Sinkovec.
    - Comic Reader: volume 1, number 102; 1973 December. (box 1)
    - Comic Reader: volume 1, number 103; 1974 January-Feb. (box 1)
    - Comic Reader: volume 1, number 106; 1974 May. (box 1)
    - Comic Reader: volume 1, number 108; 1974 July. (box 1)
    - Comic Reader: volume 1, number 109; 1974 August. (box 1)
    - Con*Tour Magazine: volume 1, number 1; 1997 July/Aug. (box 1)
      Editor: Collin Wood.
    - Con*Tour Magazine: volume 1, number 2; 1998 January. (box 1)
      Editor: C. W. Hall.
    - Con*Tour Magazine: number; undated. (box 1)
    - Crystal Ship: number 8; 1984. (box 1)
      Editor: John D. Owen.
    - Crystal Ship: number 9; 1984 October. (box 1)
    - Cullowhee Comments: number 1; 1974 February. (box 1)
      Editor: Richard D. Llewellyn.
    - Cutter's Goose: number 1; 1985 May. (box 1)
      Editor: Marilyn Johansen.
    - Cutter's Goose: number 2; 1987 May. (box 1)
  - D - E
    - Death Realm: number 4; 1987 Winter. (box 1)
      Editor: Mark Rainey.
    - Death Realm: number 11; 1990 Spring. (box 1)
    - Decal: number 3; 1973 May 18. (box 1)
    - Decal: number 5; 1975 February. (box 1)
      Editor: Donald E. Cochran.
    - Dee-Pice: number; 1989. (box 4)
      Editor: Patricia D Ames.
    - Dio: volume 1, number 4; 1979 October. (box 1)
    - ECCE: number 1; 1972 november. (box 1)
      Editor: Roger D. Sween.
    - ECCE: volume 2, number 1; 1973 Spring. (box 1)
    - ECCE: volume 2, number 2; 1973 Summer. (box 1)
    - Empire for the SF Writer: volume 8, number 2; 1983 Summer. (box 1)
      Editor: Millea Kenin.
  - F
    - Fandom Unlimited: volume 1, number 1; 1971. (box 1)
      Editor: Richard D. Larsen.
    - Fantastic: number 7; 1967 April. (box 4)
    - Fantasy: volume 4, number 4; 1992 Spring-Summer. (box 4)
      Editor: Marion Zimmer Bradley.
    - Fantom Alterations: number 1; 1985 August. (box 1)
      Editor: Alex Covan.
    - Fantom Alterations: number; 1985 March. (box 1)
    - Fantom Alterations: number 2; 1986 May. (box 1)
    - File 770: number 25; 1981 April 25. (box 1)
      Editor: Mike Glyer.
    - File 770: number 26; 1981 July 30. (box 1)
    - File 770: number 28; 1981. (box 1)
    - Firefly: number 3; 1976 June 7. (box 1)
      Editor: Klaus Haisch.
    - Frantic Fanzine: number 1; undated. (box 1)
      Editor: Rosemary Walker.
    - Future Life: number 10; 1971 May. (box 1)
      Editor: Ed Naha.
  - G
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 8, number 3; 1985 March. (box 1)
      Editor: Joe Sokola.
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 8, number 4; 1985 April. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 8, number 5; 1985 May. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 8, number 6; 1985 June. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 9, number 1; 1985 July. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 9, number 2; 1985 August. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 9, number 3; 1985 September. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 9, number 6; 1985 December. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 10, number 4; 1986 April. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 10, number 5; 1986 May. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 10, number 6; 1986 June. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 11, number 1; 1986 July. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 11, number 2; 1986 August. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 11, number 3; 1986 September. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 11, number 4; 1986 October. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 11, number 5; 1986 november. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 11, number 6; 1986 December. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 12, number 5; 1987 May. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 12, number 6; 1987 June. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 13, number 1; 1987 July. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 13, number 2; 1987 August. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 13, number 4; 1987 October. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 13, number 5; 1987 November. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 13, number 6; 1987 December. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 14, number 1; 1988 January. (box 1)
    - Galactic Dispatch: volume 14, number 2; 1988 February. (box 1)
    - Ghost Riders: number 3; 1986. (box 1)
      Editor: Donna Chisholm.
    - Ghost Riders: number 5; 1988. (box 1)
    - Ghost Riders: number 6; 1989. (box 4)
    - Glyphs of the Sacred Stone: number; undated. (box 1)
      Editor: Greg Jones.
    - Godless: number 4; 1973 Summer. (box 1)
      Editor: Bruce D. Arthurs.
    - Grip: number 22; 1985. (box 1)
      Editor: Roberta Rotgow.
    - Grip 26: number 26; 1987. (box 1)
      Editor: Roberta Rogow.
    - Guying Gyre: number 3; 1975 Spring. (box 1)
      Editor: Gil Gaier.
    - Guying Gyre: number 4; 1975 Fall. (box 1)
    - Guying Gyre: number 5; undated. (box 1)
  - H - I - J
    - Hackzine: number 62; 1990 September. (box 4)
      Editor: June E Vigil-Storm.
    - Hauppauge Procrustean: number 2; 1984 June. (box 1)
      Editor: H. G. Wells.
    - Hoof Strikes: volume 5, number 2; 1987 June. (box 1)
      Editor: Sharon Matola.
    - Hyperion: volume 4, number 4; 1973 Summer. (box 1)
      Editor: Mark Jenkins.
    - Illusions: number; 1980 Winter. (box 1)
      Editor: Catherine Mintz.
    - Illusions: number; 1981 Winter. (box 1)
    - Illusions: number; 1981 Spring. (box 1)
    - Iniquities: volume 1, number 3; 1991 Autumn. (box 4)
      Editor: Buddy Martinez.
    - J.O.G.A.: number 8; 1986 December. (box 1)
      Editor: Bob Kindle.
    - Jewels and Binoculars: number 13; 1982 August 22. (box 1)
      Editor: Tom McGovern.
  - K
    - Kallikanzararos: number 7; 1973 August. (box 1)
      Editor: John Ayotte.
    - Kallikanzararos: number 8; 1974 August. (box 1)
    - Karass: number 1; 1974 January. (box 1)
      Editor: Linda E. Bushyager.
    - Kwalhioqua: number 5; 1973 April. (box 1)
      Editor: Ed Cagle.
    - Kwalhioqua: number 6; 1973 May. (box 1)
    - Kwalhioqua: number 7; 1973 June. (box 1)
    - Kwalhioqua: number 8; 1973 July/Aug. (box 1)
    - Kwalhioqua: number; undated. (box 1)
  - L
    - Lan's Lantern: number 11; 1981 July. (box 4)
      Editor: George J Laskowski Jr..
    - Lan's Lantern: number 12; 1983 April. (box 4)
    - Lan's Lantern: number 13; 1983 August. (box 4)
    - Lan's Lantern: number 14; 1984 May. (box 4)
    - Lan's Lantern: number 15; 1984 August. (box 4)
    - Lan's Lantern: number 31; 1989 August. (box 2)
      Editor: George Laskowski.
    - Lan's Lantern: number 35; 1990 September. (box 4)
    - Lan's Lantern: number 36; 1991 March. (box 4)
    - Lan's Lantern: number 37; 1991 May. (box 4)
    - Lan's Lantern: number 39; 1991 August. (box 4)
    - Lan's Lantern: number 38; 1992 July. (box 4)
    - Lan's Lantern: number 40; 1992 September. (box 4)
    - Lan's Lantern: number 41; 1993 July. (box 4)
    - Love and Rockets: number 1; 1982 Fall. (box 4)
      Editor: Gilbert Hernandez.
  - M
    - Maybe: number 28; 1973 July. (box 2)
      Editor: Irvin Koch.
    - Maybe: number 30; 1973 July. (box 2)
    - Maybe: number 40; 1974 August. (box 2)
    - Maybe: number 65; 1983 May. (box 2)
    - Maybe: number 31; undated. (box 2)
    - Midnight Graffiti: number 3; 1989 Spring. (box 2)
      Editor: James Van Hise.
    - Monolith: number 3; 1973 April. (box 2)
      Editor: Dave Mitchell.
    - Mythpring: volume 10, number 1; 1974 July. (box 2)
      Editor: Glen GoodKnight.
    - Mythpring: volume 10, number 2; 1974 August. (box 2)
  - N
    - Nekromonikon: number 7; 1982 September. (box 2)
      Editor: Neil Kaden.
    - New Libertarian Notes: number 21; 1973 May. (box 2)
      Editor: Samuel Konkin.
    - New Libertarian Notes: number 24; 1973 August. (box 2)
    - NexGen Pulp: number; 2008 June/July. (box 2)
      Editor: Michael Critzer.
    - Niekas: number 26; 1981 May. (box 2)
      Editor: Edmund R. Meskys.
    - Niekas: number 35; 1987. (box 2)
    - Niekas: number 36; 1988. (box 2)
  - O - P
    - Our Yeserdays: number; 1973 September. (box 2)
      Editor: Joann Burger.
    - Owlflight: number 1; 1981. (box 2)
    - Owlflight: number 4; 1983. (box 2)
    - Oxytocic: number 9; 1974 Feb-Mar. (box 2)
      Editor: Michael Shoemaker.
    - Pandora: number 23; 1989 Summer. (box 2)
      Editor: Meg McDonald.
    - Paper Rockets: number 1; 1983. (box 2)
      Editor: Jeff Wilcox.
    - Paper Rockets: number 2; 1985. (box 2)
    - perceptions: number 3; 1973 November. (box 2)
      Editor: Warren Johnson.
    - Phosphene: number 1; 1975. (box 2)
    - Phosphene: number 2; 1975 Summer. (box 2)
    - Phosphene: number 3; 1976 January. (box 2)
    - Photon: number 8; 1974 January. (box 2)
      Editor: Steve Beatty.
    - Photon: number 9; undated. (box 2)
    - Pirate Writings: volume 5, number 2; 1997. (box 4)
      Editor: Edward J McFadden.
    - Poor Richard's Almanack: number 1; 1999. (box 2)
      Editor: Todd Dashoff.
    - Poor Richard's Almanack: number 2; 2000. (box 2)
    - Poor Richard's Almanack: number 3; 2000. (box 2)
    - Poor Richard's Almanack: number 4; 2001. (box 2)
    - Poor Richard's Almanack: number 5; 2001. (box 2)
    - Prehensile: number 6; 1972 November. (box 2)
    - Prehensile: number 9; 1973 May. (box 2)
    - Prehensile: number 12; 1974. (box 2)
    - Psychozort: number 1; 1973. (box 2)
      Editor: Larry Nibert.
  - Q - R
    - Q36k: number; 1983 August. (box 2)
      Editor: Marc Ortlieb.
    - Radix: number 2; 1976 January. (box 2)
      Editor: Ron Rogers.
    - Radix prelude: number; 1975 July. (box 2)
    - Rally: number 31; undated. (box 2)
      Editor: Lon Atkins.
    - Rally: number 32; undated. (box 2)
    - Rastus: number 2; undated. (box 2)
    - Rebel Yells: volume 2, number 2; undated. (box 2)
      Editor: Guy Lillian.
    - Rune: number 74; 1986 February. (box 2)
      Editor: M.K. Digre.
    - Rune: number 76; 1987. (box 2)
      Editor: Jeanne Mealy.
    - Rune: number 77; 1988 January. (box 2)
    - Rune: number 78; 1988. (box 2)
    - Rune: number 79; 1989 January. (box 2)
  - S
    - Scavengers Newsletter: number 79; 1990 September. (box 2)
      Editor: Janet Fox.
    - Severed Tales: number; 1988 October. (box 2)
      Editor: Donald L. Miller.
    - Shadow of the Monolith: number 39; 1975 January 12. (box 2)
      Editor: Eric Larsen.
    - Shadow of the Monolith: number 40; 1975 February 9. (box 2)
    - Shadow of the Monolith: number 41; 1975 March 8. (box 2)
    - Shadow of the Monolith: number 38; undated. (box 2)
    - Shamrock Market Report: number 3; 1990 September. (box 2)
      Editor: Shannon Riley.
    - Short Form: volume 2, number 1; 19. (box 2)
      Editor: Orson Scott Card.
    - Short Form: volume 1, number 1; 1987 Winter. (box 2)
    - Short Form: volume 1, number 2; 1988 February. (box 2)
    - Short Form: volume 1, number 3,4; 1989. (box 2)
    - Short Form: volume 2, number 2; 1989 August. (box 2)
    - Short Form: volume 2, number 3; 1989 October. (box 4)
    - Sidetrekked: volume 2, number 16; 1983 Dec-Jan. (box 4)
      Editor: John Anderson.
    - Smile Awhile with Flojoy: number 14; 1973 April-May. (box 2)
    - So It Goze: number 6; 1974 March. (box 2)
      Editor: Tim C. Marion.
    - South Pacific Penguin: number 1; 1988 February. (box 2)
      Editor: Lon Levy.
    - Southern Fandom Confederation Bull: number 10; 1974 March. (box 2)
      Editor: Meade Fierson.
    - Southern Fandom Confederation Bull: number 26; 1982 January. (box 2)
    - Space and Time: number 19; 1973 July. (box 2)
      Editor: Gordo Linzner.
    - Space Grits: volume 1, number 1; 1983 Spring. (box 2)
      Editor: J.R. McHone.
    - Space Grits: volume 1, number 2; 1983 Summer/Fall. (box 2)
    - Starship Express: volume 1, number 1; 1987 January. (box 2)
      Editor: Phil De Parto.
    - Starship Express: volume 1, number 4; 1987. (box 2)
    - Starship Express: volume 1, number 6; 1987. (box 2)
    - Starship Express: volume 1, number 7; 1987. (box 2)
    - Starship Express: volume 2, number 2; 1988. (box 2)
    - Strange Punch: volume 1, number 5; 1981 July. (box 2)
    - Strange Punch: volume 1, number 6; 1981 August. (box 2)
    - Strip: volume 1, number 8; 1990 May. (box 4)
      Editor: Dan Abnett.
    - Strip: volume 1, number 9; 1990 June. (box 4)
    - Strip: volume 1, number 10; 1990 June. (box 4)
    - Strip: volume 1, number 11; 1990 July. (box 4)
    - Swoon: number 1; 1974 March 15. (box 2)
      Editor: Arnie Katz.
  - T - Te
    - Tabebuian: volume 1, number 1; 1973 February. (box 3)
      Editor: David Jenrette.
    - Tabebuian: number 2; 1973 March. (box 3)
    - Tabebuian: number 3; 1973 May. (box 3)
    - Tabebuian: number 5; 1973 August. (box 3)
    - Tabebuian: number 6; 1973 September. (box 3)
    - Tabebuian: number 7; 1973 November. (box 3)
    - Tabebuian: number 8; 1973 December. (box 3)
    - Tabebuian: number 10; 1973. (box 3)
    - Tabebuian: number 11; 1974 March. (box 3)
    - Tabebuian: number 12; 1974. (box 3)
    - Tabebuian: number 13; 1974. (box 3)
    - Tabebuian: number 14; 1974 July. (box 3)
    - Tabebuian: number 15; 1974 September. (box 3)
    - Tabebuian: number 16; 1974 November. (box 3)
    - Tabebuian: number 18; 1975 March. (box 3)
    - Tanjet: number 13; 1983 February. (box 3)
      Editor: Greg Hills.
  - The - The M
    - The Chicago Offender: number 2; 1981. (box 1)
      Editor: Steve (Genocide) Duff.
    - The Comic Art Showcase: number 1; 1970 April. (box 1)
    - The Green Pages: number; 1989 August. (box 1)
      Editor: Chester De Roors.
    - The Green Pages: number; undated. (box 1)
    - The Incredible Mantra Comic: volume 1, number 2; 1974 Summer/Fall. (box 2)
      Editor: Steve Kester.
    - The Insomniac: volume 14, number 102; 1980 April. (box 1)
      Editor: Zaharakis.
    - The JDM Bibliophile: number 14; 1970 August. (box 1)
      Editor: Len and June Moffatt.
    - The JDM Bibliophile: number 16; 1971 August. (box 1)
    - The Jinnia Clan Journal: number 51; 1981 July. (box 1)
      Editor: Steve Stanley.
    - The Matalan Rave: number 2; 1983. (box 2)
      Editor: Michael Hailstone.
    - The Matalan Rave: number 4; 1984 February. (box 2)
    - The Mystic Muse: volume 1, number 1; 1987 Spring. (box 2)
      Editor: James Waltz.
  - The N
    - The National Fantasy Fan: number; 1983 April. (box 2)
      Editor: Owen K Laurion.
    - The National Fantasy Fan: number; 1983 August. (box 2)
      Editor: Robert Osman.
    - The National Fantasy Fan: number; 1983 December. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: number; 1984 February. (box 2)
      Editor: David Heath.
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 44, number 3; 1984 June. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 46, number 5; 1986 October. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 47, number 2; 1987 April. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 47, number 3; 1987 June. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 47, number 4; 1987 August. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 47, number 6; 1987 December. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 49, number 4; 1989 August. (box 2)
      Editor: Donald Franson.
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 50, number 2; 1990 April. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 50, number 5; 1990 October. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 51, number 6; 1993 June. (box 2)
      Editor: Tim Gatewood.
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 53, number 1; 1993 February. (box 2)
      Editor: Craig Boyd.
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 53, number 2; 1993 April. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 53, number 3; 1993 June. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 53, number 4; 1993 August. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 36, number 1; undated. (box 2)
      Editor: Joanne Burger.
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 34, number 1; 1974 February. (box 2)
      Editor: Stan Woolston.
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 34, number 2; 1974 April. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 34, number 3; 1974 June. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 34, number 6; 1974 December. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 35, number 6; 1975 December. (box 2)
    - The National Fantasy Fan: volume 51/52, number 2015-06-01T00:00:00; 1991/1992 Dec/Jan. (box 2)
    - The National fantasy Fan Federation: volume 1, number 2; 2001 September. (box 4)
      Editor: Janine Stinson.
    - The National fantasy Fan Federation: volume 2, number 1; 2002 June. (box 4)
    - The Neo-Fan's Guide: number 3rd ed; 1973 August. (box 2)
      Editor: Bob Tucker.
    - The Nightmare Express: volume 3, number 11; 1988 November. (box 2)
      Editor: Lance Brown.
  - The O - The Z
    - The Off World Connection 2: number 2; 1986 December. (box 2)
      Editor: P.E. Kinlock.
    - The Paladin's Affair: number; 1986. (box 2)
    - The Reasonable Freethinker: number 2; 1994 June. (box 4)
      Editor: Tom Feller.
    - The Southern Fandom Handbook: number; undated. (box 2)
    - The Southern Fandom Handbook: number; undated. (box 2)
    - The Spellbinder: volume 1, number 4; 1986. (box 2)
      Editor: Paul Burdick.
    - The Subterranean Unicorn: volume 1, number 2; undated. (box 2)
      Editor: Fafnir (puesdum).
    - The Wizard's Wand!: volume 1, number 4; 1987 August. (box 3)
      Editor: Philip DeParto.
    - The Wizard's Wand!: volume 1, number 5; 1987. (box 3)
    - The World According to Garth: number 5; 1983 Summer. (box 3)
      Editor: Garth Spencer.
  - Ti - Tm
    - Tightbeam: number 30; 1981 March. (box 4)
      Editor: Ingrid Maack.
    - Tightbeam: number; 1982 March. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number; 1982 June. (box 4)
      Editor: Owen Laurion.
    - Tightbeam: number; 1982 September. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 38; 1983 Summer. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number; 1983 September. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 133; 1984 August. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 134; 1984 October. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 134; 1984 December. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 144; 1986 July. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 145; 1986 September. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 146; 1986 November. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 147; 1987 January. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 148; 1987 March. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 149; 1987 May. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 150-151; 1987 July-September. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 12; 1987 November. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 153; 1988 January. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 154; 1988 March. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 155; 1988 May. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 156; 1988 September. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 162; 1990 February. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 164; 1990 July. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 165; 1990 September. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 166; 1990 November. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 167; 1991 January. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 169; 1991 May. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 170; 1991 July. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 171; 1991 September. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 172; 1991 November. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 172; 1991 November. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 178; 1991 November. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 177; 1992 September. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 183; 1993 September. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 185; 1994 January. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 186; 1994 March. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 187; 1994 May. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 189; 1994 September. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 190; 1994 November. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 191; 1995 January. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 192; 1995 March. (box 4)
    - Tightbeam: number 193; 1995 May. (box 4)